// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following shows information dissemination?",
    answer: "a. announcing through the radio",
    options: [
      "a. announcing through the radio",
      "b. applauding the performers onstage",
      "c. buying groceries",
      "d. rallying for a cause"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which communicative function serves to inspire and influence?",
    answer: "b. motivation",
    options: [
      "a. emotional expression",
      "b. motivation",
      "c. regulation and control",
      "d. social interaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What communicative function is used in most people’s daily activities?",
    answer: "d. social interaction",
    options: [
      "a. control and regulation",
      "b. information dissemination",
      "c. motivation",
      "d. social interaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What communicative function is involved when your teacher gives the coverage of the final exam?",
    answer: "c. information dissemination",
    options: [
      "a. control and regulation",
      "b. emotional expression",
      "c. information dissemination",
      "d. motivation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following situations shows control and regulation as a communicative function?",
    answer: "b. a policeman directing the traffic",
    options: [
      "a. a news anchor delivering the headlines",
      "b. a policeman directing the traffic",
      "c. a young girl selling fresh flowers at the market",
      "d. boys sharing adventure stories"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Accommodating visitors during town fiestas uses the social interaction function of communication.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Teachers motivate students by shouting at them when they are wrong.",
    answer: "B.False",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A man speaking in front of the crowd with his head down looks very confident.",
    answer: "B.False",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Misunderstanding may occur when there is misinterpretation of gestures.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Body posture is not important when a speaker wants to show confidence.",
    answer: "B.False",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Facial expression can help to express a message better.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Emotional expression, as a function of communication, is used to influence or persuade another person to act.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "A person’s emotional state does not affect his or her perception of a situation.",
    answer: "B.False",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Students’ questions are not important to facilitate a good class discussion.",
    answer: "B.False",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "You can express yourself better if you choose your words well.",
    answer: "A.True",
    options: ["A.True", "B.False", "C.Halfway True", "D.Halfway False"]
  },
];
